http://www.joyfulheart.com/admin/privacy_policy_popup.htm

Privacy Policy
We respect the privacy of our newsletter subscribers, customers, contacts, those who answer our surveys, and those who fill out our questionnaires. It is our policy:
Choice and consent. To respect the purpose for which our site visitors gave us information. We give users choice and consent over how their personal information is used, and remove names immediately upon request.
Third party use. To not sell, rent, or loan our subscriber or customer lists to third parties for e-mail marketing. While we sell advertising in our e-mail publications to other companies, we never allow third parties any other use of these subscriber lists.
Unsubscriptions. To send our periodicals only to those who
request them (that is, opt-in). We immediately unsubscribe those who request
it through convenient unsubscribe links in every e-mailing. Our welcome
message to subscribers and every issue of our newsletters clearly explain
how to unsubscribe. We keep our subscription lists as clean as possible to
prevent obsolete e-mail addresses from taking unnecessary bandwidth.
Cookies. To use cookies in a responsible manner to help our visitors, not snoop on them. We use cookies (1) to help rotate banner advertising, (2) to identify shoppers with their shopping carts, (3) to make it easy to order a second time, (4) to allow subscribers to store passwords in cookies if they desire, (5) to give proper credit for sales made through links on our affiliates' sites, and (6) to prevent users from experiencing our pop-up subscription box more than once. We do NOT collect or use information from cookies to develop a profile about our visitors or shoppers.
Security. To store subscriber and password files with personal information in a secure manner. We store such files in areas not accessible to Web browsers, behind password protection, or off-line.
Termination. To continue this policy beyond the termination of our company. If a majority portion of the assets of our company were to be acquired by another organization, that might include our subscriber and other lists, but only as part of a clear agreement binding that organization to abide by the spirit and letter of our privacy policy.
These policies apply to all websites owned by Joyful Heart Renewal Ministries
and Wilson Internet Services, including  doctorebiz.com, joyfulheart.com, and jesuswalk.com. If you have any concerns or questions about our privacy policy or information collected on our sites, please
contact Dr. Ralph F. Wilson and he will reply promptly.
